iridium.com 2019-07-06

# Iridium Privacy Policy | Iridium Satellite Communications

### Our Commitment to Privacy

Iridium Satellite LLC (“Iridium,” “we,” or “us”) understands that privacy is important to you and values your trust. This privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) explains how we handle and protect online information about you. By using this website or any of the Iridium Apps (the “Site”) or the services provided through this Site (the “Services”), we may collect information about you, and use and disclose such information as described in this Privacy Policy. Your use of the Site or Services indicates your acceptance of the terms of this Privacy Policy.

Most areas of the Site are intended for consumers. One area of the Site – Iridium for Partners – is restricted to use by our Service Partners. This Privacy Policy describes Iridium’s collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information and Anonymous Information (each as defined below) in both the consumer areas of the Site and within Iridium for Partners. “Personal Information” means your personal data or personally identifiable information, such as your name, address, email address, telephone number, job title, job industry, company/organization name, and any other information you voluntarily provide or any other non-public information that we associate with your contact information and that can identify you as an individual. “Anonymous Information” means information that we do not link to Personal Information and does not enable contact with any identifiable person. This Privacy Policy applies to Iridium’s handling of Personal Information and Anonymous Information collected via this Site and not to data obtained from other sources. For Iridium’s processing of personal data from users of Iridium’s services contracted from a third party of the European Union, please see our [Iridium Service Provider GDPR Privacy Notice](https://www.iridium.com/iridium-service-provider-gdpr-privacy-notice/).

THE SITE AND SERVICES ARE PROVIDED FROM THE UNITED STATES, CANADA AND OTHER LOCATIONS. IF YOU ARE A USER ACCESSING THE SITE OR SERVICES, PLEASE BE ADVISED THAT THROUGH YOUR CONTINUED USE OF THE SITE OR SERVICES, WHICH ARE GOVERNED BY UNITED STATES LAW AND THE APPLICABLE LAW OF OTHER JURISDICTIONS, THIS PRIVACY POLICY, AND OUR TERMS OF SERVICE, YOU ARE TRANSFERRING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION TO THE UNITED STATES, CANADA AND OTHER LOCATIONS, AND YOU CONSENT TO THAT TRANSFER. ADDITIONALLY, YOU UNDERSTAND THAT YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION MAY BE PROCESSED IN COUNTRIES (INCLUDING THE UNITED STATES AND CANADA) WHERE LAWS REGARDING PROCESSING PERSONAL INFORMATION MAY BE DIFFERENT OR LESS STRINGENT THAN IN YOUR HOME JURISDICTION.  

### Children’s Information

This Site is intended for adult use only. We do not direct any part of our Site to children less than 18 years old, nor do we knowingly collect Personal Information from children.  

### We Collect Personal Information

In the consumer areas of the Site, we collect Personal Information when you knowingly provide it to us. In order to use, access, or receive certain Services, you may be required to complete the applicable registration form accessible on the Site. For example, to receive a newsletter or press release, you must register and provide your name, email address, job title, job industry, and company/organization name. To send a satellite message using our Services, you will be required to register and provide the number to which you are sending the message, your email address and a message. To inquire about products, technical support, and customer service or sales support, you will be required to provide your name and email address, and your mailing address if desired. In addition, we collect Personal Information when you participate in surveys and/or sweepstakes, or when you correspond with us. When you contact us to inquire about certain products or to learn more about becoming a partner, you must provide your name, company name, job title, email address, phone number, the product or solutions you are interested in and the service partner with which you are affiliated (the “Service Partner”), if applicable.

To gain access to Iridium for Partners, you will be required to register and provide certain Personal Information, including your name, email address, mailing address, phone number and extension, citizenship, job title and the Service Partner. In order to expedite your registration, and for verification purposes, it is possible that we may obtain certain Personal Information about you from the Service Partner, such as your name, email address, mailing address, phone number and extension, job title, and/or citizenship. Iridium collects the information you provide via Iridium for Partners, including information you provide on behalf of a Service Partner.

When you use our online store, you will be required to provide your name, mailing address, phone number and credit card information.  

### Anonymous Information Collected Via Technology

When you use the Site or Services, we collect certain Anonymous Information, such as your Internet protocol address, browser type, operating system and host domain. We may also use cookies or similar technology and navigational data like Uniform Resource Locators (URLs) to automatically gather statistical data that helps us improve our Site and deliver a better and more personalized service. For example, we may collect the date and time of access to the Site, the areas or pages of the Site that you visit, frequency and amount of time you spend viewing the Site, and other communication data.

As further described in our Cookie Policy, Iridium uses cookies and other similar technologies (e.g., web beacons, pixels, ad tags and device identifiers) to recognize you and/or your device(s) on or across different Services and devices. We also allow other third parties to use cookies as described in our Cookie Policy. You can control cookies through your browser settings and other tools. For more information on the cookies we collect and how to disable them, please visit our [Cookie Policy](https://www.iridium.com/iridium-cookie-policy/).  

### The Ways We Use Information

We use Personal Information that you submit to us for a variety of business purposes, such as when use is necessary to entering into or to perform a contract with you (i.e. deliver and manage Iridium for Partners for our Service Partners, administer your Iridium for Partners account or provide you with our Services), complying with a legal obligation (i.e. provide our investors with required information about us), or when there is a legitimate interest pursued by us or a third party (to the extent it does not infringe on any data subject’s fundamental rights and freedoms). Use of your Personal Information under a legitimate interest include to respond to your requests, provide you with technical or sales support, notify you about changes to our Services or our Site, improve the quality of the Site and Services, ensure compliance with applicable law, or manage our everyday business needs, such as auditing, administration of our services, analytics, and the enforcement of any corporate reporting obligations, [Terms of Use](https://www.iridium.com/terms-of-use/), or other policies.

Pursuant to valid consent provided by you, we may communicate with you to provide information that may be useful or interesting to you. Such information may include newsletters/press releases and marketing communications, including contest entries and surveys. You can opt out of receiving newsletters/press releases from Iridium by clicking the “Unsubscribe” link at the bottom of the email. If you are a user of Iridium for Partners and receive marketing emails from us, you can opt out of receiving future marketing messages by modifying the relevant setting in your profile. Please note that to the extent you are using other Service(s) or are a Service Partner, even if you unsubscribe or opt-out to marketing emails, you may still receive transactional, relationship or service related emails (e.g., emails related to your transmission of satellite messages).

We may also use your Personal Information to create Anonymous Information by removing information that makes the information personally identifiable to you (such as your name or email address). We may use these records, and other Anonymous Information, to analyze usage patterns in order to enhance the Site and Services, and tailor them to your preferences.  

### The Ways We Disclose Information

We may disclose Personal Information or Anonymous Information:

  * To contractors, third party vendors, and other third parties who help us make the Site or Services available or who support our business;
  * To third parties to whom you ask us to send Personal Information, including those to whom you send a satellite message;
  * To certain Service Partners so they may approve your access to their proprietary information available on Iridium for Partners or for other business purposes;
  * To our parent company, any subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under common control (collectively, “Affiliates”);
  * To a company that merges with, acquires, or purchases the assets of Iridium, in which case such company may continue to process your Personal Information as set forth in this Privacy Policy; or
  * If we believe in good faith that such disclosure is necessary to: (a) resolve disputes, investigate problems, or enforce our Terms of Use; (b) comply with applicable laws or respond to requests from law enforcement or other government officials; or (c) protect or defend the rights or property of Iridium, you, or third parties.

### Updating Your Personal Information

You may update your Personal Information if you have registered at iridium.com by emailing us at [iridium.online@iridium.com](mailto:iridium.online@iridium.com) from your email address on record or, if you have access to Iridium for Partners, by editing your profile within Iridium for Partners. We may not be able to update any information previously disclosed to a third party. Your Personal Information is necessary in order for us to send you newsletters or other communications or to provide you access to Iridium for Partners. Therefore, if you delete such necessary information we may not be able to provide you certain Services.  

### Personal Information Rights of Residents of the European Economic Area

If you are a resident of the European Economic Area, you have the right to request from us access to, and rectification and erasure of your Personal Information. You also have the right to restrict or object to processing concerning your Personal Information, which includes restricting us from continuing to process your Personal Information under certain circumstances.  In addition, you have the right to data portability, which includes certain rights to have your Personal Information transmitted from us to another data controller.

When the collection and processing of your Personal Information is based on consent (in particular, in the case of marketing communications), you have the right to withdraw your consent at any time.

To exercise or to inquire about the above rights you can send an email to [dataprivacyadministration@iridium.com](mailto:dataprivacyadministration@iridium.com). ** _  _**You also have right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority.  

### Security of Personal Information

We have implemented appropriate measures designed to secure your Personal Information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration, and disclosure.  We will take reasonable steps to ensure that your data is treated securely and subject to appropriate safeguards in accordance with this Privacy Policy and applicable legislation.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information over the Internet is not completely secure, and therefore we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to us through our Site and shall not be liable for breaches of security or integrity, third-party interception in transit, or any damage caused to you or your company, your computer(s), or other property by accessing or using our Site or Services.  

### Third Party Practices

The Site or Services may contain links to other websites, including those of our partners. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the online content of such third parties. The privacy policy of a partner listed on our Site may differ from ours. We encourage you to read the privacy policy of each third party website you visit before sharing your information with that third party.  

### Retention of Personal Information

Unless otherwise required by law, we will erase Personal Information when it is no longer necessary in relation to the purposes for which it was collected or otherwise processed; when you withdraw your consent (where lawfulness of processing was based on your consent) and there is no other legal ground for the processing; when you object to the processing and there are no overriding legitimate grounds for the processing; and when it is necessary to comply with legal obligations.  

### Changes to Our Policy

This Privacy Policy is subject to revision from time to time. We will post any revised version of the Privacy Policy on this Site. If we make material changes to how we treat your Personal Information, we will notify you through a notice on the Website home page. Any amended Privacy Policy will be effective as of the date stated in the revised policy.

Continued use of our Site or Services following notice of such changes will indicate your acknowledgement of such changes and agreement to be bound by the revised terms and conditions.  

### Contact Us

Iridium Satellite LLC is an independent controller of your personal information. If you have any questions regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us at [iridium.online@iridium.com](mailto:iridium.online@iridium.com).

  _**Last Updated: August 2018**_
